Father,
my imprisonment has taught me
how stupid I've been until now.
I didn't keep my greed in check
and I stole many times.
I'm ashamed of who I was.
I was able to change thanks to you, Father.
Please, help me get
parole.
Recent studies have shown
that with proper training,
even dogs and parrots
can learn to read, make a fire
and understand art.
If that's the case,
what difference is there
between man and animal?
What do you think?
I don't know.
But, about my parole...
Excuse me.
– But...
– I've got it.
The idea is to avoid the pit
of the first cherry
while eating the second one.
Not biting into the first pit
when eating the second cherry.
And what do you think of my parole?
I think it's possible.
Really, Father?
I'll give your name to the committee.
Thank you, Fa...
I've come to like you.
You'll never learn, will you?
A disposition toward evil
can never be corrected.
However,
I mustn't reject
that talent of yours.
You'll be useful to me.
I can't let Jotaro's Stand
leave this prison, after all.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
S'il y a une chose que je sais, c'est qu'il n'y a pas de temps pour pleurnicher
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
J'atteindrai le fil de l'espoir, je l'attraperai et je continuerai mon chemin
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
S'étendant tout autour de toi, esquive les pièges et la haine
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
Personne ne peut arrêter mes jours de survie
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
Éloigne-toi de (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Je ne veux pas dire, (C'est impossible)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
C'est parti, compte, (Un, deux, trois)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
Emmène-moi loin, (Vole ! Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
Tant que je suis sincère avec moi-même
(Got to be tough)
(Je dois être forte)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Explose ! (Hey) Je suis bien debout (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Je ne veux plus redevenir celle que j'étais avant
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Explose ! (Hey) Peu importe combien (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
D'attaques habiles me mettent à mal
genkai wa houkai
Je surpasse mes limites
Give up wa rongai
Hors de question d'abandonner
unmei tenazukeru made
Jusqu'à ce que le destin soit de mon côté...
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Je n'arrêterai pas de frapper, n'arrêterai pas de frapper
Don't stop beating 'em up
Je n'arrêterai pas de les frapper
Episode 9  Marilyn Manson, the Debt Collector
What do you mean, F.F. is hiding it?
I thought that disc was important,
that it contained your father's Stand.
Doesn't it bother you
not to know where she's hiding it?
– We don't know if we can trust her...
– This place is great!
– So different from the swamps!
– Let's calm down.
I want to play too.
We do say "playing catch", right?
I trust F.F.
and Whitesnake doesn't know
she's alive.
It's the safest way.
Very well.
But what would be even better
– would be to give it back to him.
– I know.
I'm not allowed any visits
or phone calls
because of my escape attempt.
I haven't figured out
how to get the disc out.
Hey, you!
That's my cup!
What's your problem?
I'm thirsty, I'm just taking a sip.
Put that cup back on the bench!
Why did you leave it there
if it's so important to you?
You should be more careful around here.
Foo Fighters, I'll bring you water!
Don't make a mess!
Give that back!
Well, well.
I have more water than before.
I'm lucky.
Well,
let's get back to our game.
– Well, well.
– What?
You've never thrown a ball, have you?
Oh, damn it.
Tuck your hips in.
A little more.
That's it.
You're already playing better.
Jolyne, did you know
we've just thrown the ball 86 times
without dropping it once?
Let's go to 100!
100 dollars says you drop it.
I bet 100 dollars.
Excuse me, but who are you?
And what do you mean, 100 dollars?
My name is Miraschon,
inmate FE26789.
I bet you 100 dollars
you won't make it to the 100th throw.
Where did that come from?
I'm just killing time.
Let's go!
Only 13 throws left!
Calm down.
I don't have that kind of money.
I can't bet that much.
You can bet anything.
Cigarettes, medication,
chewing gum, phone calls,
a massage vibrator...
I accept anything of value.
Let me be clearer.
I never gamble.
Wait.
Jolyne,
we should take that bet.
We could make some money.
Take my money.
F.F. might be useless,
but at this rate, we'll win.
Come on, Hermes!
You think it's a trap
set by Whitesnake.
But I'm on the same floor as Miraschon,
I know her well.
She's just a small-time crook,
a kleptomaniac.
Think about it.
Even once your punishment is lifted,
you'll need money
to make phone calls.
So,
are we playing or not?
I want to play! We can win!
Fine.
But you don't have 100 dollars,
do you?
If you cause trouble or get too close,
the bet is off.
It has already started.
But it would be unfair to me
if you stood too close
or held the ball too long.
We'll stay three meters apart
and throw within ten seconds.
Very well.
Let's play, come on!
Take your time to aim.
You have ten seconds to throw.
That's 89!
Only 11 throws to go!
Get away from my cup, bitch!
F.F.!
That was close.
Focus!
Not my fault!
She tried to take my cup!
I'm just looking.
Get away from my cup, I said!
Very well.
Five more seconds.
F.F., throw the ball!
– Damn it, she's distracting me!
– Hey!
I'll hold your cup.
– One second left.
– Hurry up!
Not this!
Jolyne!
It was close, but she got it!
Sorry.
I told you to focus.
It won't happen again.
See? A hundred throws!
Well done.
I can do 100 more.
See? That was an easy bet.
Hand over your 100 dollars.
Wait, she bet with F.F. too.
That makes 200 dollars.
That's right. She owes us 200 dollars.
Cough up the bills.
One more zero if you can't do
another 100 throws.
You heard me right.
I'm betting 1,000 dollars.
Are you serious?
Do you even have that much?
Of course I do.
But like I said,
I also accept
anything of value.
Same rules as last time.
Okay?
No. I'm done playing with you.
Let's be clear.
There's something fishy about you.
– If you want to bet, go play somewhere else...
– Deal.
Nice.
– F.F., give me the glove and the ball.
– Yes.
Hermes, no!
Jolyne, she's suspicious.
Especially with her habit
of insisting on betting.
But...
MINT
we could make 1,200 dollars.
I can't pass up such an opportunity.
Careful.
The game begins
the moment you agree to play.
Ten seconds go by fast.
– Hermes!
– F.F.!
More easy money.
Thirty.
Thirty-one.
Thirty-two.
Great, the next one will be the 33rd.
Inmates,
put down your recreational equipment.
Recreation time is over!
Five...
F.F.!
– Thirty-three!
– Bitch!
I'll make you behave!
The bet is off. Understood?
Imagine a meteorite
falling straight from the sky
onto this courtyard at this very moment.
You can't help it,
it's the meteorite's fault.
That's what you'd say
to convince yourself,
not to convince me.
But does that work for you?
Maybe you took too long
to throw the ball.
If you can honestly say
you didn't break
the rules of the game,
then of course,
back out of the bet.
Goddamn it.
Hermes,
you're going to end up in the punitive ward.
Please, sir.
Give me five... no, three minutes.
I'll do another round,
finish up in two minutes.
F.F., hurry!
But your 100 dollars
only cover the ball.
I'll take the glove back. Hand it over!
What?
Goddamn it!
Damn it...
I stuck a sticker on it
for this kind of situation!
Hermes!
Let's keep playing.
I'm just watching.
I won't interfere.
And I can't prove it, but...
Hermes...
She knows what she did.
There's no doubt
she just broke
the rules of the game.
If I know it,
it's because Marilyn Manson,
the debt collector, has appeared.
Hermes!
She's a Stand user!
Marilyn Manson collects debts
no matter where the money is hidden.
Money, or anything of value.
That's not enough.
Kiss...
Game over.
Hermes!
Hermes...
If I sell this liver on the black market,
it will cover the remaining 590 dollars.
Bitch!
Take this!
I am the shadow of Hermes' conscience.
You can't hurt me.
Hermes broke the rules
and lost the bet.
I only collected her debt.
If you have anything else of value,
I'm willing to trade her liver
for it.
The game isn't over.
What?
A thousand throws.
If I win,
you give back everything you took from her.
Everything.
Fine. But I hope you're ready
to stake something of equal value.
– Got it.
– Very well.
The game has begun.
I'll be back.
F.F.!
– Jolyne.
– Hermes,
it's not your fault.
Miraschon is a Stand user.
Whitesnake must be behind all this.
She's surely here to take
my father's disc from me.
So don't play this game.
You're caught up
in my problem with my father.
I can't let you die.
But what are we going to do?
A thousand throws? That's impossible!
This Stand looks invincible.
You're right.
We're going to beat Miraschon, the user!
The Stand might be invincible,
but Miraschon isn't.
That's why she left.
Let's go!
She's here.
She must have entered this room.
There's a door in the back.
She could have escaped through there.
F.F.!
Jolyne, don't throw!
Damn it!
F.F.! The ball is coming toward you!
Where is she?
– I can't see a thing!
– Don't move!
The ball is going to hit you!
Damn it! I've got it!
That was close!
Nice one, F.F.
Now calm down and throw.
I'm right here!
– Where?
– Hurry!
They're done for.
F.F.!
No time for this crap!
Foo Fighters
I threw
toward her voice.
I didn't even aim!
Damn it! What is her power?
Lockdown is about to begin.
All inmates to their cells.
Prepare for roll call.
I repeat!
She went right!
It's really too bad.
You're cornered.
Now that we know you have a Stand,
I won't hold back my punches.
Wait,
I'll give everything back.
The liver
and the money!
That's not enough.
Who gave you that Stand?
What?
Whitesnake.
It was him, wasn't it?
I want to know who his user is.
What are you talking about?
Don't mess with me.
I'm serious!
All I wanted
was to get out on parole!
What is this?
A freight elevator.
It carries food from the cafeteria.
How many seconds do you have left?
Six...
No, five?
Jolyne!
Two seconds...
F.F., the ball!
Throw it to me!
Damn it!
What will be your next choice?
Eight seconds.
Seven, six...
F.F.!
Are you okay, Miraschon?
That was so easy.
Don't hesitate to ask me again.
The game...
has been interrupted.
It's over,
Jolyne Kujo!
Marilyn Manson takes everything,
no matter the cost!
Wherever it is,
even if it's lost,
Marilyn knows where it is.
Jolyne!
I'll take your most expensive organ,
and the remaining debt will be covered
by your most precious item,
your father's disc.
And that disc...
is being hidden by that woman!
I've won!
Your organ,
your disc...
are mine now!
The game is far from over.
But how?
The ball...
You're not allowed.
– You broke the rules.
– No.
We never specified
who I had to play with.
I can play with a guard.
The debt collector agrees.
How many throws do I have left?
Eight hundred?
Nine hundred?
Too hard to count.
Let's say 1,000 throws.
We did it!
MIRASCHON
STAND NAME:
Marilyn Manson, the Debt Collector
HAS BEEN TAKEN OUT OF THE GAME...
I'll give my father his disc back.
I'll also get him the disc
held by Whitesnake,
no matter what it costs me.
Même si tu penses que je fais face
Although you think I cope
Ma tête est remplie d'espoir
My head is filled with hope
D'un quelconque endroit autre qu'ici
Of some place other than here
Même si tu penses que je souris
Although you think I smile
Intérieurement et pendant tout ce temps
Inside and all the while
Je m'interroge sur mon destin
I'm wondering about my destiny
Je pense à
I'm thinking about
Toutes les choses
All the things
Que j'aimerais faire
I'd like to do
Dans ma vie
In my life
Je suis un rêveur
I'm a dreamer
Un lointain songeur
A distant dreamer
Rêvant d'espoir
Dreaming far away
Dès à présent
From today
The Savage Garden Plan
(To the courtyard!) (1)